Hello hello friends this video made yesterday got a
little busy okay so for a
while I got busy in chaos
no-no I was able to update it so generally I
try to update the results that came
and this video is not because today
stockpile one on cent of a in vwe crown
nagar subscribe subscribe so
now as far as the principle of mine is concerned
you will see in half of my videos you will
write in my videos a principal which is
queen white sesame it includes 1956 shell that
if it is there then the
important thing is that
now you are happy so if you are tracking it
why white sesame I will take it
here
write in we had made a video
conference hall you will remember this is okay
white sesame
so cancel cancel has both A potential
and HD stitching exit
maxims I did not do the recipe
because these companies A potential and
like it definitely Veer One India okay third
third subscribe and subscribe this video
works in its favor subscribe it
works a little you can subscribe digitally
I had set up my life little by little by doing appointments, okay acid and now if
we look at it, then it is called
that this is a company, now the results that used to come,
many people said that this is a very bad
result, nothing special, this is okay, so
their profit profit is from 13 -
6, okay, but yes,
but what happened is that
we do not understand all these other things, okay,
generally don't right to go inside data
because data can be important, it should be
written in lines, so right now profit profit,
so what will you do here,
subscribe to data profit net profit and
in its last quarter till 304, if you did
not subscribe then subscribe ghr ghr
problem tips, the business was
that
percentage, so 2% ULIP and that is why HDFC
Life valuation is two times pencil,
why single regency, otherwise even today they
collect better premium, it
also makes better profit from it, due to which, but we were
not able to understand this thing and write this black properly.
From Unit-2
traditional demand fiction okay very
important if you see it then this famous year
ago I quickly saw 2% 42% and especially the
picture of idiots after one hour and that it is
growing at five percent is amazing and
something important and every time I
talk then the most important thing is to
understand that internet network subscribe to network
network data input
artificial intelligence and customers,
okay why is this happening, so
whoever is seeing the market is
thank you will be introduced protection
business production business is growing so fast, is
n't it good persistence is very good
you must know by percentage there is a presence, the
more persistent it was okay, it
means it tells how many old
customers came back okay old customers coming back like this
it is considered that
you branded time people have lot of faith in your
brand okay lakh people are coming first
second bike all our creams are late and we will make new ones
okay Prem
I have just started talking about settlement ratio so that you can
use it in every insurance company, but the
maximum
claim settlement ratio that this insurance company shows us, out of the number that we got,
we have
set it for 97.9, this is a
big thing, Karona music fashion is getting
spoiled, that is why there is renewal off,
okay, but the thing is that Addison had business for half an hour, okay,
what happens with this, a
Tilak competition at the same time, all this brand
building, resettlement bill, okay,
22% loss in new business and very
important questions have come,
product mix, now look, this
is the link, till then the certificate which is Titu Titu Titu
Titu, this from above, which you set 108 times time to time,
bring it to the front, the name was
5866, size small, so in these districts,
okay, no one can even imagine that it has so much reach, that
means even Vanilla does not have the power, I
say, okay, as much power as
ICC has, cardamom has the same.  LIC is not passed,
this is run by Muslims, patience, gentlemen,
okay and we are the opposition team, team
product from online, give money to
subscribe, this is the time of technology,
maintain market share from the market, if it happened in this way, then it is
almost the biggest company in your private sector, we are
showing persistence,
our persistence is increasing, the more it increases, it
means that it is doing very well, okay,
everyone has matched it, subscribe,
then the skin is
white and it should be a person,
from 206 number downwards, that motivational reserve
of 32 days, disposal in subscribing to this channel,
but this is the biggest thing,
subscribe to it, subscribe, everyone got to know,
subscribe, so sometimes home, now
subscribe for school, the money was there,
which means, theirs has now become furious, which means, which has become
thick, how to
keep it around 20 percent, keeping ULIP down is
also very important, then come down from the flat, so
see this here, this is and it is very
important, its ulterior product
subscribe to it,
this Max Max Lock Neeraj Kumar has
replaced it  In the name-giver, there is an opinion about how many
people have become small but it is taking a lot of time for this term insurance
and it is very much that how should we
maintain it but they are not taking risk, it is much
less than what they were doing,
okay, it was okay that the
pension related thing is great, their pension fund,
pension, those who are taking these 16 years, they are going along well, is there
any tension in it, they
want to make a long-term sustainable
growth serum, for that absolutely a long term
system is needed and a strong distribution
system, the customers themselves have not come,
hence it is also very important for them, so what they are
doing, the channel product,
I have to do that the war about which the
subscription,
then the bank insurance, the noise is increasing
rapidly for the channel, along with this, there is something
not to talk about, mother profit, that is
Vidmate Chakli minute plane, the total
balance of their account 459 producers have
taken 450 crores till now, okay and 5334
center in-charges should not be appointed,
whatever was needed, all the things should be done very
quickly  going to sleep